
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow:yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00F7EEFF,&HF0000000,&H00D50EF1,&H320E5BCF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000040,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00C64FA4,&HF0000000,&H00F4DBED,&H320F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruGothic-Md,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H000F0F0F,&HFF8080FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,30,30,10,1
Style: edcn,微软雅黑,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H000F0F0F,&HFF6A00D5,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,30,30,10,1
Style: opjp,DFGPOP1-W5,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004D04F7,&H00D604FB,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,10,128
Style: opcn,方正卡通简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004D04F7,&H00D604FB,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.07,0:01:39.92,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由雪酷字幕组制作 仅供交流 若您喜欢请支持购买正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.07,0:01:39.92,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}对本片制作有任何建议或意见 欢迎至雪酷论坛(http://bbs.sc-ol.com/)参与讨论
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.07,0:01:39.92,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译：海马  米国       校对：饭团      后期：SS
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.51,0:01:46.34,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(665,375)}{\fad(300,300)}{\blur2\bord2}「A Man？Woman？\N~渐渐改变着的人们~」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.82,0:02:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜游的好快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.09,0:02:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.83,0:02:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比较擅长体育嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.53,0:02:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入游泳部吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.97,0:02:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.12,0:02:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大赛比赛时也许会赢呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.53,0:02:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那个时候没有攻击亚健妲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.33,0:02:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果梦梦那时候没有赶到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.73,0:02:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许就被干掉了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.89,0:02:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.17,0:02:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始就不该靠自己一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.69,0:02:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该依赖下朋友…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.98,0:02:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依赖朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.89,0:02:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚 我们的确是为了互相战斗而被制造出来的生物兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.47,0:02:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我们的生活方式也不仅限于此
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.25,0:02:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你真心想把我当做亲人来对待的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.83,0:02:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人与人的接触
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.80,0:02:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能了解那种温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.57,0:03:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的温暖…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.64,0:03:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为了我们彼此之间能互相了解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.25,0:03:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.19,0:03:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止我都是一个人生活着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.18,0:03:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人说过这就是我该走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.52,0:03:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.34,0:03:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见了吗 我游泳的身姿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.29,0:03:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.52,0:03:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好像没有精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.73,0:03:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点事…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.12,0:03:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和姐姐吵架了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.36,0:03:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.52,0:03:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚也有姐姐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.84,0:03:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦 过不了多久就会和好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.40,0:03:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.49,0:03:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有时也总和梦梦闹矛盾吵架什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.67,0:03:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知不觉的就又在一起聊起来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.11,0:03:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟姐妹不都是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:03:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.40,0:04:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜和梦梦从很久以前就一直在一起了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.37,0:04:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.04,0:04:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚 对不起 我说了什么不该说的话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.60,0:04:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在心情很复杂吧 小暗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.66,0:04:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.79,0:04:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我该做什么 心里很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.21,0:04:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗 那样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.30,0:04:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于杀手亚健妲的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.69,0:04:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小暗只告诉了我和梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.09,0:04:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于黑咲芽亚的事也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.86,0:04:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗组织创造出来的第二代变身能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.66,0:04:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像小暗的妹妹一样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.80,0:04:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.26,0:05:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚就跟过去的我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.64,0:05:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为生物兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.21,0:05:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始终相信着只有黑暗世界是我们的归宿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.69,0:05:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 如果可以的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.74,0:05:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让她也明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.65,0:05:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这颗星球上所体验到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.51,0:05:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 她也一定会…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.04,0:05:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白小暗你的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.46,0:05:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我还是会把她当做危险人物来看待哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.02,0:05:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的哦 梦梦公主
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.17,0:05:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是这种喜欢防着别人的那种类型
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.54,0:05:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽不知道是否能和你友好交往
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.89,0:05:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你还是很可靠的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.26,0:05:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉这说法让人高兴不起来呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.45,0:05:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 塞利奴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.85,0:05:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.72,0:05:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.87,0:06:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 能不能过来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.23,0:06:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样… 感觉芽亚心情更加低落了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.93,0:06:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有什么事 我能为她做的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.87,0:06:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和姐姐吵架…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.12,0:06:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和小暗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.74,0:06:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 在听我说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.71,0:06:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.26,0:06:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.22,0:06:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做一些让她感觉很有趣的事情怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.59,0:06:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很有趣的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.95,0:06:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前小的时候 美柑失落不高兴的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.03,0:06:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就做些鬼脸什么的 不管什么总之要让她笑就好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.73,0:06:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心情低落的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.28,0:06:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要一笑 就会恢复精神 心情就会变得舒畅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.76,0:06:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要让她笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.60,0:06:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣的事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.04,0:06:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试试看 谢谢啦 梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.80,0:07:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.19,0:07:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菈菈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.41,0:07:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.62,0:07:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想打个招呼但是还是犹豫了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.78,0:07:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 帮助娜娜消除烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.14,0:07:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没有 也没说什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.52,0:07:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜她啊 别看她那样 其实很天真的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.80,0:07:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不习惯的班级里 第一个成为朋友的芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.64,0:07:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对她来说一定很特别
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.75,0:07:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.32,0:07:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望她们能顺利和好呢  娜娜和芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.70,0:07:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.43,0:07:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小暗也是 变化那么大 肯定没什么问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.76,0:07:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小暗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.21,0:07:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么说小暗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.32,0:07:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.68,0:07:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有东西想让我看 到底是什么 娜娜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.38,0:07:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管了 快来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.72,0:07:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了 看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.97,0:08:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小狗干什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.60,0:08:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是春菜的宠物 叫做西连寺马隆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.19,0:08:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的脸很搞笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啊 好怪的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚的事情已经跟你说过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.00,0:08:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我哄她高兴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.70,0:08:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜你拜托我那就没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.13,0:08:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后要给我两根牛肉干哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.11,0:08:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好软
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.69,0:08:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软绵绵的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.99,0:08:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉啊 春菜 你明明有社团活动的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.70,0:08:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 马隆也很高兴出来散步
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.10,0:08:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜她真体贴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.49,0:08:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要帮朋友打起精神来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.76,0:08:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.57,0:08:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨斗 梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.79,0:09:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得本命的春菜也在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.80,0:09:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要表现一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.77,0:09:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么啊 梦梦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.87,0:09:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顾娜娜我一个人就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.01,0:09:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 梦梦也一直担心着娜娜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.51,0:09:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 这回给你介绍我的宠物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.27,0:09:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在宇宙各地认识的动物们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.57,0:09:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.09,0:09:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是各种各样都有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.92,0:09:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.87,0:09:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之挑了一些可爱的叫出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.44,0:09:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子 好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.92,0:09:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑咲芽亚那张笑脸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.19,0:09:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是发自内心的高兴着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.43,0:09:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}我舔 我舔 我舔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.79,0:09:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.31,0:09:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个奇怪的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.93,0:09:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔功不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.92,0:09:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔主人 这是作为一只狗 最至高无上的爱情表现
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.75,0:09:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能输
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.12,0:10:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看着吧 本大爷的舌技
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.58,0:10:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.68,0:10:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我舔 我舔 我舔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.93,0:10:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.43,0:10:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 马隆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.91,0:10:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么舔 芽亚会很困扰的…但好像也不是这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.78,0:10:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙 太嚣张了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.36,0:10:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也有作为宠物的尊严啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.07,0:10:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个 往哪里钻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.71,0:10:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住…不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.57,0:10:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.91,0:11:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜 黑咲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.77,0:11:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.74,0:11:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西连寺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.75,0:11:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.35,0:11:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西连…等…现在就…救…哦啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.87,0:11:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.91,0:11:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结城 不要拉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.27,0:11:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 身体不受控制啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.99,0:11:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这相当的下流啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.50,0:11:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是兴奋的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.38,0:11:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止 你们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.52,0:11:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.99,0:12:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜梨斗他们正处于相当赞的…啊 不对
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.45,0:12:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当糟糕的状况啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.84,0:12:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.51,0:12:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.79,0:12:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传唤装置不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.14,0:12:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.02,0:12:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来 把那个还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.11,0:12:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.31,0:12:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住你了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.48,0:12:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.06,0:12:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.16,0:12:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果使用变身能力的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.53,0:12:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的身份就会暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.64,0:12:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是管不了那么多了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.00,0:12:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要救娜娜才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.60,0:12:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这个破坏掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.06,0:13:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.85,0:13:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐…姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.13,0:13:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是千钧一发啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.05,0:13:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.73,0:13:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惹出这么大的乱子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.74,0:13:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没事的 娜娜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.95,0:13:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.06,0:13:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚也…那个…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.48,0:13:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要抱歉啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.16,0:13:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常高兴哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.12,0:13:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物真棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.17,0:13:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有舔舔也不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.78,0:13:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回请您来舔我吧 结城学长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.81,0:13:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢 芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.49,0:13:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来进展的不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.16,0:13:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜她呢 想看到芽亚打起精神的样子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.20,0:14:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.68,0:14:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜…是为了我…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.53,0:14:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.45,0:14:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸口好温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.58,0:14:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是姐姐她说过的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.96,0:14:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然芽亚也是个好孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.39,0:14:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要加入后宫候补吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.83,0:14:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在说那种话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.01,0:14:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.82,0:14:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就现在来看还有太多不安定因素
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.44,0:14:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.62,0:14:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果可以 那还是最理想的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.23,0:14:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果将芽亚吸纳入我们的阵营
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.75,0:14:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那在她背后操纵的主人 也不得不行动了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.30,0:15:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金色之暗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.96,0:15:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你是要把芽亚引导为人类吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.54,0:15:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是姐妹之情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.61,0:15:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于兵器来说是多余的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.91,0:15:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这份感情却可以利用
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.71,0:15:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从至今为止发生的事情让我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.06,0:15:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有必要改变做事方法了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.56,0:15:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金色所不知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.22,0:15:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论多么憧憬人类
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.34,0:15:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都无法违背作为兵器的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.82,0:15:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 小暗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.70,0:15:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.37,0:15:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑咲芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.54,0:16:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 芽亚 什么时候和小暗关系这么好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.33,0:16:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.66,0:16:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近好像开始和娜娜以外的同学说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.45,0:16:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前明明一点兴趣都没有的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.46,0:16:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一看就好像是地球上的普通女生一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.17,0:16:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.66,0:16:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦梦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.53,0:16:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 今天要和我们去卡拉ok吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.59,0:16:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.25,0:16:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在男孩子面前唱歌很不好意思啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.56,0:16:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿到小伦的泳装海报了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.31,0:16:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去校长室慢慢欣赏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.15,0:16:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要用心眼看 这泳装就和透明的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.37,0:16:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀哈 伦伦伦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.78,0:16:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伦？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.74,0:16:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.58,0:16:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们学校的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.18,0:17:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是很有名的偶像哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.60,0:17:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.55,0:17:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是菈菈的青梅竹马哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.98,0:17:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说她是外星人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.80,0:17:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是梅莫鲁西星的王族
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.70,0:17:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然外表是一个人 其实是双胞胎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.81,0:17:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要打个喷嚏
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.09,0:17:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会在女生的伦和男生的莲之间互相转换
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.54,0:17:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很稀有的种族哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.36,0:17:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在男生和女生之间转换…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.08,0:17:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.50,0:17:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.26,0:17:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.50,0:17:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变男变女君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.79,0:17:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨斗学长变成女生了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.94,0:17:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像这样「啪」的一下转变了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.95,0:17:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要为了说明就随便把人家变成女生啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.83,0:17:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上把你变回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.46,0:17:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 变男变女君好像没电了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.17,0:17:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.69,0:18:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 随着时间的经过自然就会变回男生了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.07,0:18:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子如果被猿山看见的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.14,0:18:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 菈菈 看见梨斗了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.12,0:18:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨子！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.21,0:18:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认错人了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.06,0:18:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下 学长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.74,0:18:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.76,0:18:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西连寺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.55,0:18:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在…在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.08,0:18:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有看见菈菈和结城吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.31,0:18:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像书包也不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.57,0:18:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.24,0:18:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有点事就早退了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.48,0:18:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早退？为什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.53,0:18:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是私奔了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.47,0:18:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私…私私私私奔？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.86,0:18:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯你激动过头了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.24,0:18:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人怎么会做这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.67,0:18:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.51,0:18:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也翘课就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.65,0:18:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候我为什么会那么认真啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.95,0:19:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我知道早退的原因了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.47,0:19:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这打扮是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.24,0:19:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是菈菈逼我穿的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.90,0:19:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为芽亚说要看梨子可爱的一面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.58,0:19:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.11,0:19:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长的胸部好大哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.83,0:19:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别揉胸部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.19,0:19:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不好的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.16,0:19:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.65,0:19:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.46,0:19:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.70,0:19:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.38,0:19:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做黑咲芽亚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.03,0:19:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为什么就跟着来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.15,0:19:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说你要跟到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.06,0:19:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为学长很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.04,0:19:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我舔一遍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.04,0:19:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别真的舔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.57,0:19:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉梨斗身边的怪人又增加了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.38,0:19:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一关要这样过哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.81,0:19:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}快住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.97,0:20:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚你要喝咖啡还是红茶？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.08,0:20:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要喝红茶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.55,0:20:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芽亚你要这样喝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.08,0:20:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是甜食派啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.27,0:20:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也想喝吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.50,0:20:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.05,0:20:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞利奴 你没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.30,0:20:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.02,0:20:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧 娜娜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.12,0:20:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在嘲弄我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.14,0:20:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我没有 你搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.62,0:20:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.72,0:20:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨斗的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.47,0:20:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为芽亚的红茶 身体和衣服都黏乎乎的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.61,0:21:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且也不是一直都这个打扮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.39,0:21:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是换掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.26,0:21:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这要怎么脱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.27,0:21:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 菈菈那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.83,0:21:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我穿那么麻烦的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.66,0:21:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静 这可是自己的裸体啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.99,0:21:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然以前也变成过女生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.89,0:21:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是不习惯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.09,0:21:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像不是自己的身体一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.29,0:21:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜娜憧憬的就是这样子的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.94,0:21:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我觉得很重很碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.84,0:22:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对女生的身体很有兴趣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.85,0:22:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是好事哦 梨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.15,0:23:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Metamorphose~改变之时~」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.82,0:00:11.40,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}信じてね 私を
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.60,0:00:16.79,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}今君にあげるよParadise
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.08,0:00:20.31,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}飛び込んで愛の園へ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.08,0:00:26.44,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}最高の夢を 一緒に見ましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.74,0:00:30.77,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}止まらない衝動 愛情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.97,0:00:33.13,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}you know？　本気でいこうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.34,0:00:36.28,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}速攻 go on 重要 Just Project
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.60,0:00:40.24,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}方法順序本当どうでもいいの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.46,0:00:42.88,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}本能でto loveって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.88,0:00:47.15,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ねえ 君のonly oneじゃなくたってIt's all right
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.38,0:00:49.81,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}みんなでHappyになろうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.07,0:00:57.43,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}受け止めてくれる？この恋は銀河で最強のSCANDAL
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.36,0:01:00.67,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}たった一人のターゲット
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.85,0:01:02.80,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}それはそう君です
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.85,0:01:06.78,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}傍で永遠にそうやって笑っていて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.94,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}信じてね 私を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.19,0:01:15.55,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}今君にあげるよParadise
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.84,0:01:18.73,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}飛び込んで愛の園へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.76,0:01:25.12,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}最高の夢を一緒に見ましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.82,0:00:11.40,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}要相信我喔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.60,0:00:16.79,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}现在马上为你献上Paradise
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.08,0:00:20.31,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}向爱的乐园奔跑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.08,0:00:26.44,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一起去做甜美的梦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.74,0:00:30.77,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}无法停止的冲动 爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.97,0:00:33.13,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}you know 要勇敢地面对
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.34,0:00:36.28,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}速攻go on启动重要的Projecet
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.60,0:00:40.24,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}方法顺序什么的真的无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.46,0:00:42.88,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}任由本能to love
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.88,0:00:47.15,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}呐 其实就是我不是你的only one也It's all right
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.38,0:00:49.81,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}大家一起得到幸福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.07,0:00:57.43,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}停得下来吗 这份爱是银河最强的SCADAL
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.36,0:01:00.67,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}唯一的目标
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.85,0:01:02.80,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}没错那就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.85,0:01:06.78,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}陪伴着我 永远地保持那笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.94,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}要相信我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.19,0:01:15.55,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}现在马上为你献上Paradise
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.84,0:01:18.73,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}向爱的乐园奔跑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.76,0:01:25.12,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一起去做甜美的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.50,0:22:19.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四角のイエローカード  ギリギリセーフ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.59,0:22:22.13,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三角関係のトラブル アウト
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.31,0:22:27.29,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君を見ると 反則したくなちゃう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.74,0:22:30.74,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ ピンチもチャンスも纏めて All right
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.96,0:22:33.63,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よい シュートもルールも読まずにいこう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.85,0:22:39.63,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君に逢うたび 全部の気持ち ずっとグルグルしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.90,0:22:48.17,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭の中 君は誰とランデブーしてるの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.40,0:22:57.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっとワクワクするレベル 試してみたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.30,0:23:00.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは恋だ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.36,0:23:04.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空より広い 海よりも深い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.80,0:23:10.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀河の果ての星の波にも収まりきらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.63,0:23:11.94,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと恋だ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.17,0:23:16.36,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否定しても 言うこと聞かない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.61,0:23:19.30,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸の鼓動が高鳴ってるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.52,0:23:23.49,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつもドキドキ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.50,0:22:19.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点被罚 四角的黄牌
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.59,0:22:22.13,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是三角关系引起的麻烦 Out
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.31,0:22:27.29,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你我就有一种想犯规的冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.74,0:22:30.74,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 不管是危机还是机会 All right
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.96,0:22:33.63,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是靠球技还是规则 上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.85,0:22:39.63,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次见到你 我就管不住我的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.90,0:22:48.17,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子里幻想着和你约会
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.40,0:22:57.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想试试更进一步的刺激
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.30,0:23:00.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.36,0:23:04.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比天还广 比海还深
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.80,0:23:10.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是银河尽头的群星 也无法匹敌
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.63,0:23:11.94,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一定是恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.17,0:23:16.36,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我怎么否定 我的心依然不听使唤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.61,0:23:19.30,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着清晰地心跳声
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.52,0:23:23.49,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是扑通扑通的


